aprilbraswell.com 2011-10-10

# Dating and Relationship Expert, Internet Dating Profile Writer and Coach | Woman Motivational Speaker - April Braswell - Privacy Policy

AprilBraswell.com and PromoteYouOnline, Inc. are committed to maintaining the privacy of our Web site visitors. You are not required to reveal any personal information, such as your name, address, or telephone number, in order to visit our Web site and access all of the free content.

It’s important to us that you understand the safeguards we have in place to make sure your privacy is protected when you visit our Web site and when you purchase product and register online for our seminars or other events.

The following information explains our Privacy Policy and describes how and to what extent we collect information when you visit this Web site.

**Log Files**

We use "cookies" (small text files that are stored on a user’s computer) to collect and store only the following non-personally identifying information about our Web site visitors: the domain name or the Internet address or the Web site from which you accessed our Web site, the date, and time of your visit. We use this information to measure the number of visitors to the site and to specific pages of it, all as part of our effort to continually improve the site and your experience here for our visitors.

**Credit Card Security**

None of the information that you send to our Web site is retained at the site. Instead, we use an industry standard technology called SSL (Secure Socket Layer) and a secure server to receive and forward your credit card information, currently through Payment industry trusted leader, PayPal. The SSL encrypts communications between your computer and their servers. This security is designed to enable you to send credit information to us via PayPal without the risk of interception. Additional information on SSL is available at http://home.netscape.com/security/techbriefs/ssl.html.

Upon receipt, your information is transferred from our Web site to a PayPal secure server for processing and storage.

AprilBraswell.com and PromoteYouOnline, Inc. collect this credit card information via PayPal to make it easier for you to purchase our products, seminars, and services online. AprilBraswell.com and PromoteYouOnline, Inc. do not use or share credit card information for any other purpose. We retain on file such information as is needed for standard accounting record keeping requirements.

If you prefer not to send your credit card information through our Web site, you can still register for any of the events listed on our Events Calendar by printing out the form and following the mailing instructions for each event.

**Regarding Your Contact Information**

If you register or contact us online, we will keep a record of your contact information in order to be able to send you occasional announcements or invitations that we believe might be of interest to you. If you do not wish to receive future communications from us, simply let us know by clicking the Unsubscribe option at the bottom of the email.

**Sharing Information With Third-Parties**

AprilBraswell.com and PromoteYouOnline, Inc. do not share, rent, or sell any information about visitors to our Web site to any third parties.

**External Links/Third-party Sites**

Our Web site contains links to external Web sites that do not fall under the AprilBraswell.com and PromoteYouOnline, Inc. domain. AprilBraswell.com and PromoteYouOnline, Inc. are not responsible for the privacy practices or content of these sites.

Please be aware that other Web sites that can be accessed through our site may collect personal information about you. You are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords or any other personal information. While we are committed to protecting your privacy while you visit our Web site, AprilBraswell.com and PromoteYouOnline, Inc. do not ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or via our site to another one.

**DISCLAIMER**

We prepared the materials and links on this web site for informational purposes. The transmission and display of the information contained at, or accessed through, this web site is not intended to create, and receipt or viewing of it does not constitute, a counselor-client relationship. Since we are not providing professional counseling through this web site, you should not act upon any information you might receive from it without seeking professional counsel.

The materials on this web site are intended, but not guaranteed, to reflect current developments in several informational fields. We do not, however, represent, warrant, or guarantee they will be complete, accurate, or up to date when you view them. AprilBraswell.com and PromoteYouOnline, Inc. are not responsible for any third-party content that may be accessed through this web site. Any reference to third-party information, products, or services linked to this web site does not constitute an expressed or implied endorsement by AprilBraswell.com and PromoteYouOnline, Inc.

This site is not intended to constitute advertising. Under the applicable laws, regulations, and ethical rules of some jurisdictions, however, the contents of this web site might be deemed to constitute advertising. We do not wish to represent anyone desiring representation based upon viewing this web site in one of those jurisdictions.
